Now, I went to the vegetable shop before that, he asked Brother Broccoli
So, Brother Bhola, why do you eat Videshi
They eat Gobi
And now I think they are a little aware of it
Because the quality of the food was also good in India
In 18th, 19th century Britishers came and only the food was not there
Alotamater, Papita, Pumpkin, Gajar, Patta, Gobi Peanuts and Mirchi
Where the friends of Mirchi were also good in India
All these vegetables were brought from India in 18th century in British people
And after many years, we have forgotten that these vegetables were from Videshi
Today, Mirchi Alotamater is our main ingredient, and we cannot imagine without it
That is why I always say that do not resist change
Because change will remain in society
And you too will forget the Sunar and Later
The question is when you will forget, fast or late
If we take history and study, then we will not be in any danger
In India, all the people who live in India were not Indians
They were from Africa, from America
Tynasors have been ruled 20 crore years in this state
And we have only been 2-3 lakhs
I am putting a video here, I will see it all