Alright, so should you learn to code or let AI do coding for you
I mean there are like crazy amount of AI tools right now that can actually take a simple
Text input and convert it into a real project
For example, let's say you want to create a dashboard for your SAS application or create
A simple to do app or maybe a not taking app, simply open one of these AI tools, give it
A simple text prompt and the code should be ready in no time
So it all started with the introduction of chat GPT
So back in the days when chat GPT was initially announced, if a person want to develop
A let's say code and HTML page with some basic styling and stuff, he could write away
Open chat GPT and ask it to code the same and chat GPT should give the code in no time
Similarly let's say some basic JavaScript project PHP Python
I mean chat GPT was capable enough to write code for all of these popular frameworks
And libraries and programming languages
After chat GPT came other AI chat boards like cloud AI which performed way better
When it comes to coding sort of things and then various different LLMS and AI models